Thank you for watching
me
No Minagae Kettei Pone
It's 2024, and in honor of last year's hard work, the program has set up a place for you to enjoy yourselves.
Tonight, please watch over the party of the youngest members who are the most restless of all the members.
Oh, no!
What is this?
Enter!
Boring.
Yeah, it's boring.
What the hell, I missed it!
What do you want?
Who's in charge?
I'll do something.
Oh, shit.
I'm nervous.
A drink.
It's not like a Menchu or anything, right?
I'm gonna surprise you.
Because the chrysalis is moving.
Because the willow is moving.
I thought you'd bring me some munchies.
No, I don't have one either.
No, thank you.
It was all wrinkled.
Aren't you going to say "cheers"?
You're mimicking the take.
I will.
Well, let's have the older one.
Okay, I'll have an okapi, please.
Okapi.
Okapi Okapi.
Thank you very much.
Seino Kempion
Kepi.
It's not Kepi.
I'm hungry.
Let's go shopping.
What's your favorite meal?
Let's go shopping
Oh, no.
It's not like we're going to get anything here.
You're going shopping?
We're going shopping.
I feel so... grown-up.
Do you want to do something?
Let's do something.
Relay the earbuds.
You know what I've been wanting to do?
We've been practicing the headphone gun relay.
So, our staff has prepared the equipment.
So, we tried it right away!
Can you connect the words that Tomisato said?
Motorcycle
Motorcycle Kawasaki Motorcycle
The microphone is mine
Motorcycle Motorcycle Motorcycle
I'll always party
You'll take anyone who says
I've made up my mind
I'll always love you
Always we party
Hooray!
Always we're part apartment
Always I'm an apartment
Next time it's Motorcycle Kawasaki Motorcycle
You've been different from the start.
It's about you.
It's never about you.
It's always been about me. It's always been about the party.
Very disrespectful.
I'd like to change teams.
I'll change teams.
Mikku is
Miss
Miku is crazy about Aya
I'm crazy about
Miku is obsessed with Aya
Mikku is
Unusual
to Aya
speak
I'm crazy about
swimsuit
With Sisara
Shisa and...
Himura.
I am
Combination
Poppi
You and
Iroha is
One of you is
One is
Happy
Your Iroha is happy
Let's have free time until everyone comes back
Let's have free time
Free time
Good morning
He's back.
I'm back.
Thank you
There's Omoke at home.
Oh, my God.
Do you know how much all this stuff costs?
A lot.
Guess.
Yes, sir.
Yes, 25,000 yen.
Eighty-six hundred yen.
No, sir.
19,000 yen
46,000 yen
No, sir.
Not that much.
What's going on with the 9,000 yen intervals?
If you do it this way...
No, sir.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
ie.
Ingredients, or something like that.
They're all good.
No, because it's so delicious and you can eat it with so much food.
Golden
Oh, I see.
I see.
Choo-choo-choo.
Can I put it on the camera?
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
LOL!
It's a gift exchange!
This time, the person doing the exchange did it, so each person brought a gift from home that they treasure, but would like to give to someone else, or a gift that they think would look good on that girl...
Each person brought a present that he or she thought of someone else, such as a present that I don't need but that girl would want.
First, Inoue will draw Tonisaku's gift, and then
Confession time
Let's all hold it for everyone
I had a crush when I saw this thimble hard at work
Please accept it
Thank you.
I found this at home.
What did Tomisato bring?
Wait, he's smiling so much!
What's that?
Um...
Mr. Kankei-san's not here.
He's in a hurry.
I don't know if that's a good thing for people who want to do it, but...
Lissachu's here.
It's one of those things.
Don't do it.
But it's nice.
It looks good on you.
And then, for the gift-giving...
A lot of members brought their favorite books.
Interesting
It's a novel. I often buy books, but I just read the words and fall asleep.
I read this one, really read it, and I can sleep 100 times out of 100.
I pinch myself and watch.
That's why.
Everyone's like an impromptu confession.
And the member zone that brought the very thing we don't need.
Nakanishi brought
A futon dryer!
He said it's very comfortable.
It's the kind that warms up the futon when it's snuggled under the covers!
Lastly, the youngest Okaba won a present!
The material
Oh, a latte.
T-shirt?
I bought a new one, so I thought I'd give it to you.
Let's go together.
It's cute.
Let's go see it together.
Slime.
Is this slime?
You can make it by hand?
It's too much!
When you stretch it out, it's like a whoosh.
Wow.
All I can see is the back of your head.
That's a lot of slime.
He's a slime fiend.
He's a slime fanatic. - He's a slime fanatic.
It was my favorite kind.
It smelled like strawberry milk and all kinds of other things.
Oh, my God.
I was trying to drink it.
Strawberry milk.
Then, after a mysterious imitation of strawberry by the same classmates
I took the liberty of presenting my personal reflections on this year's "Kensetsu-zhunchu" recording.
I'll announce what I'm personally reflecting on in this year's construction work recording.
I have.
We had a thing where we had to decide who would be the donkuser.
And as it turned out, I came in first.
I was asked to make a closing comment.
I'm really sorry about the low-level fight today, and you said, "See you next week.
But you know what, I'm in first place, and I'm having the lowest level of competition, and you're saying, "Well, I'm sorry about that.
What was I saying?
I'm so sorry.
I get nervous when Hina guesses.
I'd say something like, "Oh, I don't know... maybe I phrased that a little wrong...
I want to be able to speak well on Hina-dan.
I mean, I'm so worried about what people will think of me when I'm first out in the world.
And yet, when I went to pray for a hit, I really stopped by and crushed it.
I still don't.
This is about not taking care of animals.
I've had people tell me that I don't take care of them in a good way, but...
It's too strong.
That one or the protector one.
The protector... for practice.
No one really spoke on the ride home.
It was a little loud, though.
I made him drink a lot.
I couldn't protect anything.
Has anyone here ever had a strong miasmatic drink?
I've never had it, but it sounds pretty bad.
It makes you think variety is real.
How many drinks did Umeda-san have that day?
Four would have killed me.
But Mr. Umeda kept telling me that I would be fine.
That kindness and all kinds of guilt made me feel guilty.
I drank in other shows, but the one in the middle of construction really killed me.
That's right.
It's different.
Under construction, the swings are huge.
Just because it's a country.
I had a cream cannon the other day, too.
Cream guns are a real thing.
321.
That was slippery.
I thought we all lost our heads.
This was amazing.
The typhoon is right in front of you.
That's so scary.
I've never had a gun pointed right at my face.
That's a first for me.
The Bargaining Game
You told me there's a terrible divestment game.
It's a terrible, terrible divisive game.
We were all really desperate not to take it.
That's why the project was so fun and interesting.
We all continued to work after that.
We all took a bath together once.
We didn't have a bath, so I had to put half of my head in the sink.
I showed up at the manager's office with my head in the sink.
I've really experienced a lot in this show.
If I hadn't joined Nugezaka, I would never have climbed Mt.
I wouldn't have been hit by a cream cannon.
I wouldn't have had to drink such a bad drink
Beriberis... no one has done that yet, right?
What else is there?
Haunted houses and screams?
I've never done it.
We haven't even been to a haunted house.
Maybe a bungee jump, then.
Let's not talk about this.
Oh, no.
I've heard it already.
Haunted houses.
Roller coaster.
Roller coasters are electric.
Haunted house will be like a regular idol.
It's like a real place where people die.
Ruins.
Ruins or tombs.
Sleep over in a ruin or a tomb.
Nogizaka Basket
Nogizaka Basket is a different kind of basket.
It was a Halloween project.
A game of "Isturi" in which the person who corresponds to the theme stands up and plays the game
I'm going to play a game of "Istri" with only the governing body.
Understand?
Understand
Understand Understand
What is the subject?
Who has ever gotten a zero on a test?
Who has?
Is there anyone like that?
I'm sure it's normal.
Do you?
Is there?
Do you have them?
All of them.
All of it.
Let me explain once and for all, because it got messy before the game.
What is this Bubu Cushion?
I've been thinking of different names for it, so I thought I'd do the Bub Cushion.
One more time.
I was just sitting here.
Ayaki, you've taken a lot of hits.
What's Ayaki's name?
You just forgot the name.
Let's put it that way.
That's right.
I was so sleepy at the time I didn't write my name.
He's cute.
It's not cute.
Here we go.
Mr. Bananaman... who prefers Mr. Kimura.
Oh!
Ooh.
Ooh
Oh!
Ooh.
If you're talking about yakiniku and sushi, you're a sushi guy.
This seems to divide them.
Surprisingly, Sugawara was the only sushi person in the 5th term
Who had a fight with their family this year?
What?
Fights.
Why did you fight?
My mom was visiting from Fukuoka, but she sulked all day.
I'll make her cry if she's in a bad mood.
What?
That's cute.
I have a pair of socks.
Okay, who's wearing socks that aren't safe today?
It's okay.
Oh, my God!
I screamed so hard.
Come on, let me see.
What did you wear?
They're the same.
Oh, my God.
What are you wearing?
Uh...
You guys.
you guys
But...
Uh...
Who?
I'm here to announce my MVP.
Oh!
Oh.
Questionnaire from everyone in advance
5th graders also voted in advance for the MVP they think was the most active in 2023, so I'll announce the best
I'll announce the top three here.
Okay, from the front.
Let's go to number three.
It's like a great audition show!
Third place.
We have three tied for third place.
First one.
Ayano Ogawa in third place.
Yay!
What's up with this whole MVP thing?
Every time I see her live, I think she's getting better and better at performing with different people.
At the Under Live the other night, she looked so energetic and cool from afar and on the monitor.
I admire you not as a peer but as an idol.
I also really like your singing.
Who doesn't like it?
No, I don't.
You just said that.
I'm really happy.
Next, in a tie for third place... is Arno Nakanishi.
I'm going to go with Aruno Nakanishi, since he started talking to me at a rapid pace this year.
Arno, who is still going at her own pace and never changes in a good way, is helping me a lot.
This is Sakura Kawasaki.
Next up was Sakura Kawasaki, who was in control of the atmosphere of the venue the moment she sang at the center of the stage at Andara.
This is Hina Okamoto.
I don't have her name.
And last in a tie for third place, Satsuki-chan Suda-hara.
Thank you, Satsuki!
I think she has changed more than anyone else in the 5th term in terms of singing, dancing and speaking.
She is very honest, so I often think that she is able to take what she thinks is good and incorporate it into herself.
I'm a cynical person, so I really envy Suda Hara's honesty, and although I don't say it often, I really like it.
This is Nagi Inoue.
I'm embarrassed to be announced.
I'm a cynical person.
Cute.
It's not that I don't say it.
Next.
I'm going to announce the second place winner.
Teresa Ikeda.
I think it's really great that she passed the entrance exam to the university while she was still active and continued to blog a lot even after going to the university!
It's really amazing!
I wonder when she sleeps... when she writes...
I really didn't know what it was, because I didn't know you were doing experiments.
I didn't even know I got in.
You didn't tell me.
I didn't know when to tell you.
We were in the cab together.
I didn't really see the acceptance announcement until Hina and I were in the cab together.
My mom called me and told me she had the number.
We were in the car.
That's really great.
First place.
It says "number one, hands down.
It says "Dantotsu No. 1.
Nana Inoue.
Thank you.
I know you must have been under unimaginable pressure as the center of "Heaven for One".
But at the live, you were so majestic and cool that I didn't feel that.
Aya Ogawa
This is embarrassing.
I feel that Nagi has become more reliable and stronger after the summer tour.
Of course, everyone is the MVP, but seeing Nagi's figure gave me a lot of power.
I'd like to cry if someone mentions her name!
I...
I won't say so.
Thank you.
It was written
Congratulations
I'm really tired.
Oh, no...
NyanNyan is going to cry
Nagi!
She's so weak, she says she's attracted to you.
I'm going to cry
She's gonna cry too much
I'll cry too much
I'll get dumped No, don't cry next to me
It says I'm number one by far
You guys are really great! Thank you so much!
I'm so sorry...
But after the summer tour...
I'm so happy to see her so excited.
But the tour's over... and I didn't join Hinaga's tour this time...
But I really think that all 11 of us have changed in a good way.
11 people including myself.
This was the second year of the tour. It wasn't the first time.
I don't think we're allowed to do anything we can't do.
Everyone was talking about how we wouldn't be allowed to do anything we couldn't do.
It was a little scary.
But the feeling that we were all working hard in the same direction was really fun.
There were a lot of times when I felt like things weren't going so well.
I'm glad this year is over.
I'm glad that this year is over, because I got to do the first live show for the first term, including the national tour.
We experienced a lot of firsts and not-so-firsts, and that's why we're so happy that this year is over.
I'm glad this year is over.
It's become a precious memory for me.
It was so intense!
I'm a clumsy person. I guess I should be blunt.
The tour was a lot of fun, but...
But to be honest, the pressure of being the center makes it hard to have fun.
But the reason Samiki and I were able to have so much fun was because of you.
Let's all have fun next year!
Thank you for all your hard work.
I wish we could've done karaoke.
Yeah, I wanted to.
You know... the kind of thing where everyone gets together and has a good time.
There's a one-person heaven.
It's nice.
MV?
Like a series of live shows.
It's good. It's good.
There's a good ending.
This is so good!
Hey, hey, hey, guys.
Where's the loneliness?
Can you get up and get excited?
Can you do it?
It's like a whole body.
I like this.
Rock-Paper-Scissors
Miron-chan
Manjun-chan.
You wouldn't eat that now, would you?
That's where it ends.
New member!
She's so nice.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Anew Landing!
Laughter
Thank you for your hard work
Applause
Great, that was a nice flow.
I like that he sang that at the end.
It's so good.
It's like coming of age.
Youth, youth, youth!
I love it.
Everyone should remember it. If you do karaoke, you should sing the song at the end for sure to tighten it up.
I was so moved, you know?
The flow of the song was really good.
It was really good!
We'll definitely sing at the end, too.
We'll definitely sing it.
We'll definitely sing!
But, Furiri, I can't believe they eat something there.
Usually at the end of the show, everyone sings and yells.
And then you eat like this by yourself, right?
It's crazy.
In that sense, we were eating all the time, too.
And of course, of course, everyone is trying their best, but each one of us has our own thoughts.
It's because of our motives that we can talk to each other, right?
Things that only we can say to each other.
Motive.
Motive number seven.
I could tell you guys were getting along really well.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm not gonna tell you in private.
Stop that cold shoulder.
Three, two, one, go.
We practiced that one over and over at karaoke.
He's getting ready to leave.
I got it!
Mobile selection for Birthday Live starts today!
I'm Miku Michinose
This year I want to go to a persimmon hut and eat lots of persimmons!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Bye bye!
[ED